tablefortwoblog.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy - Table for Two® by Julie Wampler

Thank you for visiting Table for Two®. Your privacy is very important to us. We are committed to protecting your personal information as we would our own. This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully before using the site or submitting any personal information to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website. By using the site, you are consenting to the practices described in this privacy policy.

##  **Policy Changes**

This policy may change without notice. You should periodically check this page to stay up to date with the latest policy. This policy is effective July 9, 2012. This policy was last updated May 7, 2018.

These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

##  **What information do we collect?**

We may collect personal information from you that you’ve voluntarily submitted to us, such as your name or email address. For example, you may voluntarily submit information to this website when signing up for newsletters or submitting a comment or submitting an inquiry via our contact form.

We may also collect anonymous information such as your IP address. Anonymous information consists of non-personally-identifiable data. For example, when you use our website, we can log your IP address, the device you are using, operating system, browser type, referring website, pages you viewed, time spent on our site, when you came to our site. We may also collect information on actions you take while visiting our website, such as what links or buttons you clicked on.

##  **When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form, enter information on our site, or simply browsing the site.

Via Cookies. Cookies are small files stored on a user’s browser by our website. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. The difference is that session cookies expire when you close your browser and persistent cookies will stay on your browser until you delete them. See more about cookies and tracking technology below.

##  **Cookies & Tracking Technologies**

Table for Two® may use cookies & tracking technologies depending on the features offered. Cookies & tracking technologies are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to this site, a visitor’s demographics, and understanding how visitors use this site.

Cookies are also to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved user-experience. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We use cookies to:

  * Keep track of advertisements.
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since everyone’s browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, it won’t affect your user-experience.

You may have also subscribed to our newsletter. All newsletters sent may contain tracking pixels. The pixel is embedded in emails and allows an analysis of the success of our marketing campaign. These tracking pixels allow us to see when you opened the email, if you opened the email, and what links you clicked in the email. This also allows the website to adapt future newsletter content to the interest of the user. This behavior is strictly confidential and will not be passed onto third parties.

##  **Email Correspondence**

When you correspond with us through email, your email address and the contents of the email is retained. We provide the same protections for these emails as we employ in all information that we have received electronically.

##  **How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you comment on a post, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To operate and maintain the website;
  * To improve our website in order to better serve you;
  * To send periodic emails that you signed up for via our newsletter;
  * To send you administrative communications, such as technical notices or updates on site policies.
  * To respond to your comments or inquiries;
  * To protect, investigate, and deter against unauthorized illegal activity.

##  **Third-party disclosure**

We use third party service providers on TableForTwoBlog.com to support our site.

Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies when they advertise on our site. The advertiser’s technology can send these advertisers information that may be contained in log files. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing Florida rental houses to someone who has been looking up airfare for Florida, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing home decor ads to someone who frequents home decor sites).

##  **Third-party links and affiliate program participation**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of each and every website you visit as this privacy policy displayed here only pertains to this website.

We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to [ **Amazon.com**](https://l.facebook.com/l.php?u=http%3A%2F%2FAmazon.com%2F&h=ATMnTKBCQpe5oFbNYFNVlZKeitIxWMuiO0d4zpPYzpL98uw66P6kBSlsmjKI0EP37Bc3wH51Npa8isbuf6wYUmcJtijtoLuaPtUYoU_EhfeUKZC8oOAPz3n6n7yKUJDmkiJ07ZizxB5xPQ) and affiliated sites. As part of this program, Table for Two can post customized links, provided by Amazon, to track the referrals to their websites. This program utilizes cookies to track visits for the purposes of assigning commission on these sales.

We are a participant of the rewardStyle Affiliate program. rewardStyle is a platform designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to various retail brands and affiliated sites. As part of this program, Table for Two can post customized links, provided by rewardStyle, to track the referrals to their websites. This program utilizes cookies to track visits for the purposes of assigning commission on these sales.

##  **Advertising**

Display Ads: we may use a third-party vendor to serve content and advertisements on our website, which may use cookies, as noted above. The use of cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet.

Retargeting Ads: from time to time, we may engage in remarketing efforts with third-party companies like Google, Facebook, or Instagram, in order to market the website. These companies use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the website. You can find out more about their usage of cookies by locating their privacy policy.

Opting out: You can opt out by visiting the [ **Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page**](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/) or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

##  **Information About Online Behavioral Advertising**

Some of the ads you see on the Web or in applications on your mobile device are tailored to your interests and based on your activity online or in the applications on your mobile device. This type of ad tailoring — sometimes called “interest-based” or “online behavioral” advertising — is enabled through various technologies, including browser cookies, mobile advertising identifiers as well as other non-cookie technologies. Tailored digital ads help support the free products, services and content you enjoy online.

You can learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising by visiting: [ **https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/**](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)

##  **Distribution of Information**

We may share information with governmental agencies, law enforcement agencies, or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

##  **CAN-SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

We collect your email address in order to:

  * Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions
  * Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our readers.

To be in accordance with CAN-SPAM, we agree to the following:

  * Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
  * Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

## Rights related to your personal information

Opt-out: you may opt-out of future email communications by following the unsubscribe link in all our emails. You may also email us at julie [at] tablefortwoblog.com to be removed from our mailing list.

Access: you may access the PII we have about you by submitting a request to julie [at] tablefortwoblog.com

Amend: you may contact us at julie [at] tablefortwoblog.com to amend or update your PII.

Forget: in certain situations, you may request that we erase or forget your PII data. To do so, please submit a request to julie [at] tablefortwoblog.com

Please note that we may need to retain certain information for our recordkeeping purposes, or when required by law.

##  **Contact Information**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

 **Table for Two, LLC**  
P.O. Box 112  
Vienna, VA 22183-0112  
United States  
julie [at] tablefortwoblog.com
